1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. click(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/btn_Forgot passwords"))
17. setText(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/txtField_Email"), "agungpriyadi")
21. click(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/btn_Send validation code to email"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
25. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/msg_ValidationCodeSuccess"), 10)
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/msg_ValidationCodeSuccess"), "Validation code sent successfully!")
33. setText(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/txtField_Validation Code"), "123456")
37. setText(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/txtField_New Password"), "123")
41. click(findTestObject("Password/Page_Forgot Password/btn_Reset Password"))
45. verifyTextPresent("Password length is 6-20 digits", false)
49. takeScreenshot()